

Jordi Schaefer Ferrer Frontend Web Developer

Barcelona
20 november 1991
(+34) 664-123-742
jschaefer21@gmail.com
github.com/JSchaefer21
www.jschaefer.com
Linkedin.com

Skills

JavaScript, TypeScript ReactJS, React-Native NodeJS, MongoDB SQL, Python, C++

Languages

Spanish · native

English · intermediate

German · intermediate

Interest

Mountainbike, hiking and outdoor activities.

ABOUT ME

Electronic engineer with experience in the automotive industry, working as a fullstack developer with React/.NET.

Why frontend? I consider myself a perfectionist with the details, I enjoy seeing the evolution of the project and interacting with my code, I am organized and I like to keep the code clean and reusable.

EXPERIENCE

FullStack Developer (.Net / SQL)

Colegio Oficial de Médicos | November 2023 – Present

• Fullstack development and maintenance of a web application (.NET with SQL) for all kinds of solutions.

Frontend Developer (React)

WAGMI venture studio | August 2022 – November 2023 | 1 year 4 months

- Frontend web application development (React and Typescript) for analysis of decentralized Web3 applications and IA's chat customizations.
- Actively participating in the Project from its beginning.
 Context provider Recharts Reactflows Material UI (MUI)

SEAT automotive testing engineer

Ferchau Engineering | Jun 2017 – November 2021 | 4 years 6 months

- Management and performance of functional, durable and fatigue test for SEAT and AUDI for multiple departments with cockpit, console, interior, trunk and bumper parts.
- Analyse and report testing results, search for solutions and optimizations of parts.
- Make protocols tests and reports for release and homologate the project.

Technical warehouse support at BMW

EDAG Engineering | July 2016 - May 2017 | Munich (Germany) | 1 year

• Management, calibration and maintance of sensors, cables and electronic components for development testing cars.

EDUCATION

Bootcamp Web Developer

Neoland | April 2022 – Jun 2022

- HTML, CSS, Javascript, ReactJS, React-Native, NodeJS, MongoDB
- Final project: Web aplication and social media designed for register and share sport activities with data visualization in real time.

CS50 Introduction to Computer Science

Harvard University · edX | February 2022

• C++, Python, SQL

Degree in Electronics and Automatic Control Engineering

Universidad Politécnica de Cataluña | September 2010 – Jun 2016

• Final project: Audio board for Arduino DUE capable of processing high resolution audio data (24bits, 48Khz) in real time.